Full funnel marketing sounds good in
theory, but execution is what matters.
I'm joined by Jasper CMO L'Oreal Lynch
to discuss how LinkedIn helped Jasper
avoid wasted marketing dollars in their
rebrand campaign.
What did a true full funnel campaign
look like in practice to you?
>> We committed to a truly balanced
approach. So, for us, that meant that we
allocated 40% of our budget to top of
funnel awareness, 30% to middle of
funnel consideration, and then 30% to
kind of bottom of the funnel conversion.
>> What role does LinkedIn play across top
of funnel awareness? [music]
>> With top of funnel awareness, a lot of
our presence on LinkedIn, including the
in-feed videos as well as everything
we're doing on CTV, is all about
changing the perception of Jasper again
from tool to trusted enterprise
platform. And that is really the
foundation of this whole rebrand because
without that, none of the conversion
even matters. So, getting that
perception right from the start is a
major piece, and that's where LinkedIn
plays a giant role.
>> How did LinkedIn enable Jasper to track
down funnel impact?
>> With LinkedIn, we were able to see how
the top of the funnel was actually
feeding the bottom of the funnel. So, we
could watch as our target audience moved
through the pipeline. [music]
We could see them engage with our top of
funnel brand awareness ads through, you
know, impressions, [music] clicks. We
could see how they engaged with our
consideration ads as well. And
ultimately, we could see at the bottom
of the funnel how they became leads that
downloaded different piece of content
that then we passed along to our sales
team where it became legitimate pipeline
and revenue.
>> [music]